VARSHA SINGH

Physiotherapist Greater Noida 08533089949

Varshakushwaha16@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/varsha-singh-04230a239 ·

PROFILE

I have been an accomplished student throughout the four years of bachelor's degree in physiotherapy with immense talent and great practical knowledge being accomplished highly motivated professional possessing strong clinical assessment and evaluation skills. Distinguished Client facing skills and experience working closely with Health care professionals to assess and treat complex conditions.

EXPERIENCE

FEB 2022-AUG 2022
INTERNSHIP, FORTIS MEMORIAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE GURGAON

OCT 2021- JAN 2022 INTERNSHIP, QIN1 NOIDA

Worked as a subject matter expert and learnt direct client handling while being closely associated with curriculum management.

SEP 2020- DEC 2020
APPRENTICESHIP, KAILASH HOSPITAL NOIDA

MAY 2018- AUG 2018
APPRENTICESHIP, YATHARTH WELLNESS MULTI- PRECIALITY HOSPITAL +
APR 2021- JUL 2021
APPRENTICESHIP, JAIN AROGYAAM

EDUCATION

APRIL 2015- JUL 2017 12TH STD, AZAD PUBLIC SCHOOL

SCORED 85%

AUG 2017- SEP 2021

BACHELORS IN PHYSIOTHERAPY, KAILASH INSTITUTE OF PARAMEDICAL SCIENCES GREATER NOIDA

CERTIFICATE

PARTICIPATED IN 6TH INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE OF PHYSICAL THERAPY AIIMS 2017 CERTIFIED IN TAPING

SKILLS

- Decision making
- Creativity
- Communication
- Effective Time Management
- Fast Learner

- Adaptability
- Ability to Work Under Pressure
- Ability to work in a team
- Clinical skills

ACTIVITIES

Social work intern, Speak up world foundation Sep 2019- Dec 2019
Involved in completing weekly tasks contributing to society

Bootcamp participant, Youth for mental health Jan 2022- Feb 2022

Subject matter expert, Blackboard radio Feb 2019- May 2019

Worked as a SME on behavior and communication skills (English) for international students.